<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Cookbook</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My Cookbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 20:16:56 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cabbage and Smoked Sausage Pasta</title>
      <link>http://example.org/cabbage-and-smoked-sausage-pasta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 20:16:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/cabbage-and-smoked-sausage-pasta/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 (16 ounce) package farfalle (bow tie) pasta 1/2 cup butter 2 cloves garlic, minced 1/4 cup olive oil 1 large head green cabbage, shredded salt and pepper to taste 1 pound smoked sausage, sliced 1/4 cup grated Parmesan cheese  Directions  Fill a large pot with lightly salted water and bring to a rolling boil over high heat. Once the water is boiling, stir in the bow tie pasta and return to a boil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>German Potato Salad</title>
      <link>http://example.org/german-potato-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 19:53:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/german-potato-salad/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 pounds potatoes, peeled and sliced 1 cup chopped onion 1 cup sliced celery 1/2 cup chopped green bell pepper 1/2 cup cooking oil 1/2 cup vinegar salt and ground black pepper to taste 6 slices cooked bacon, crumbled 2 tablespoons chopped fresh parsley  Directions  Combine potatoes, onion, celery, green bell pepper, oil, vinegar, salt, and pepper in a slow cooker. Cook on Low 5 to 6 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homemade Italian Beef</title>
      <link>http://example.org/homemade-italian-beef/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 22:16:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/homemade-italian-beef/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  3 pounds beef chuck roast 3 (1 ounce) packages dry Italian salad dressing mix 1 cup water 1 (16 ounce) jar pepperoncini peppers 8 hamburger buns, split  Directions  Place the roast into a slow cooker, and season with Italian dressing mix. Pour in the water. Cover, and cook on High for 6 to 7 hours. During the last hour, shred the meat with two forks - if it does not shred easily, cook longer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snickerdoodles</title>
      <link>http://example.org/snickerdoodles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 21:47:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/snickerdoodles/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 cup shortening 1 1/2 cups white sugar 2 eggs 2 3/4 cups all-purpose flour 1 teaspoon baking soda 2 teaspoons cream of tartar 1/2 teaspoon salt 2 tablespoons white sugar 2 teaspoons ground cinnamon  Directions  Preheat oven to 375 degrees F (190 degrees C). In a medium bowl, cream together the shortening and 1 1/2 cups sugar. Stir in the eggs. Sift together the flour, baking soda, cream of tartar, and salt; stir into the creamed mixture until well blended.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crab Ceviche</title>
      <link>http://example.org/crap-ceviche/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 21:40:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/crap-ceviche/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 (8 ounce) package imitation crabmeat, flaked 2 large tomatoes, chopped 1 red onion, finely chopped 1/2 bunch cilantro, chopped 2 limes, juiced 3 serrano peppers, finely chopped 1 tablespoon olive oil salt and pepper to taste  Directions  Place the shredded imitation crab into a glass or porcelain bowl. Plastic or metal are not recommended. Stir olive oil into the crabmeat until well coated, then stir in the cilantro, onion, tomato and serrano peppers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homemade Chicken Ramen</title>
      <link>http://example.org/chicken-ramen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 20:05:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/chicken-ramen/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients Chicken  4 Chicken Breasts (boneless) 2 tbsp unsalted butter Salt and Pepper  Broth  4 tsp sesame or vegetable oil 4 tsp fresh ginger, minced 6 tsp fresh garlic, minced 6 tbsp low-sodium soy sauce 4 tbsp mirin 8 cups rich chicken stock 1 1/2 cups fresh shitake or bella mushrooms Sea Salt (to taste)  Noodles  6 (2-3oz) packs of dried ramen noodles  Extras  6 Eggs 1 cup scallions or green onions, tops sliced optional: fresh jalapeno slices  Directions  Cook the chicken: Preheat the oven to 375 degrees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olive Chicken Rollups</title>
      <link>http://example.org/olive-chicken-rollups/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 19:34:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/olive-chicken-rollups/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 1/4 lbs deli smoked chicken 8 flour tortillas (8 inches) 8 ounces (1 package) cream cheese, softened 8 ounces ( 2 cans x 4 ounces each) chopped green chilies, drained 4 1/4 ounces (1 can) chopped ripe olives, drained 2 ounces (1 jar) diced pimientos, drained 1/4 teaspoon garlic powder 1/4 teaspoon chili powder 1/4 teaspoon hot pepper sauce Salsa or Picante sauce, optional  Directions  Step One  Sub Step One   Step Two Step Three Step Four Step Five Step Six  Footnotes </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deviled Eggs</title>
      <link>http://example.org/deviled-eggs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 19:13:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/deviled-eggs/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  6 Eggs 1/4 Cup Mayonnaise 1/4 onion, finely chopped 1 teaspoon white vinegar 1 teaspoon yellow mustard 1/8 teaspoon salt 1 dash hot pepper sauce Black pepper Paprika, for garnish  Directions  Place eggs in a medium saucepan and cover with cold water. Bring water to a boil and immediately remove from heat. Cover and let eggs stand in hot water for 10 to 12 minutes. Remove from hot water, cool and peel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Precuetta Wraps</title>
      <link>http://example.org/prucetta-wraps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 20:28:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/prucetta-wraps/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1/2 Avacado sliced Second Ingredient 1 Third Ingredient Fourth Ingredient Fifth Ingredient  Directions  Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Line a baking sheet with parchment paper.  Sub Step One or Notes   Arrange the prosciutto slices on the baking sheet so they don’t touch, and bake them in the preheated oven until crisp, 6 to 8 minutes. Remove from the oven, and let cool.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
